Guide to the Jewish Labor Committee Records, Part I WAG.025.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Administrative and Organizational Records
  - Subseries I:C: Correspondence
    - Sub Subseries 1C1: General
      - Correspondence: General, Jul 1945-Dec 1945 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence: General, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence: General, Jan 1947-Jun 1947 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence: General, Jul 1947-Dec 1947 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence: Exec. Committee, 1934-1939 (Box 3, Folder 16)
        Reel#: 6
      - Correspondence: Exec. Committee, 1940-1947 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence: Exec. Committee, 1944-1947 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence: Office Committee, 1940-1947, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Cables/Telegrams, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Jan 1945 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Feb 1945 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Mar 1945 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Apr 1945 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Cables/Telegrams, May 1945 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Jun 1945 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Jul 1945 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Aug 1945 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Sep 1945 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Jan 1946-Feb 1946 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Mar 1946 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Apr 1946 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Cables/Telegrams, May 1946 (Box 4, Folder 1)
        Reel#: 7
      - Cables/Telegrams, Jun 1946 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Jul 1946 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Aug 1946 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Sep 1946 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Oct 1946-Nov 1946 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Dec 1946 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Jan 1947 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Feb 1947 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Mar 1947 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Apr 1947 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Cables/Telegrams, May 1947 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Jun 1947 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Jul 1947 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Aug 1947 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Sep 1947 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Oct 1947 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Cables/Telegrams, Nov 1947-Dec 1947 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Sub Subseries 1C2: Individuals
      - Baskin, Joseph, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Baskin, Joseph, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Baskin, Joseph, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Chanin, Nathan, 1942-1944 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - Chanin, Nathan, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - Chanin, Nathan, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - Chanin, Nathan, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - Dennen, Leon, 1942-1944 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Epstein, Lasar, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - Epstein, Lasar, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Epstein, Lasar, 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - Epstein, Lasar, Jan 1947-Jun 1947 (Box 4, Folder 30)
        Reel#: 8
      - Epstein, Lasar, Jul 1947-Dec 1947 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - Epstein, Melech, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - Epstein, Melech, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - Estrin, Samuel, 1940-1947 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      - Gebiner, Benjamin, 1935-1940 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - Gebiner, Benjamin, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - Gebiner, Benjamin, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - Gebiner, Benjamin, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      - Gebiner, Benjamin, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - Godson, Joseph, 1944-1946 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - Godson, Joseph, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 41)
      - Goldman, Paul, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 42)
      - Held, Adolph, 1938-1940 (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - Held, Adolph, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 44)
      - Held, Adolph, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 45)
      - Held, Adolph, 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 1)
        Reel#: 9
      - Held, Adolph, 1946-1947 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Honig, Camille, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Kaplan, Jerry, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Kissman, Joseph, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Kissman, Joseph, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Kissman, Joseph, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Kissman, Joseph, 1942-1943 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Kissman, Joseph, 1944-1946 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Kissman, Joseph, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Levine, Benjamin, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Levine, Benjamin, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Levine, Benjamin, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Meed, Vladka, 1946-1947 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Minkoff, Isaiah, 1936, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Minkoff, Isaiah, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Minkoff, Isaiah, Jan 1940-Aug 1940 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Minkoff, Isaiah, Sep 1940-Dec 1940 (Box 5, Folder 18)
        Reel#: 10
      - Minkoff, Isaiah, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Minkoff, Isaiah, 1943-1947 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Panken, Jacob, 1942-1945 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Pat, Emanuel, 1941, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Pat, Jacob, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Pat, Jacob, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Pat, Jacob, Jan 1941-Jun 1941 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Pat, Jacob, Jul 1941-Dec 1941 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - Pat, Jacob, Jan 1942-Jul 1942 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - Pat, Jacob, Aug 1942-Dec 1942 (Box 5, Folder 28)
        Reel#: 11
      - Pat, Jacob, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - Pat, Jacob, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - Pat, Jacob, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - Pat, Jacob, Jan 1946-Mar 1946 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Pat, Jacob, Apr 1946 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Pat, Jacob, May 1946-Dec 1946 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Pat, Jacob, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Salert, Irving, 1945-1948 (Box 6, Folder 5)
        Reel#: 12
      - Schwartz, Pinchos, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Schwartz, Pinchos, Jan 1944-Jun 1944 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Schwartz, Pinchos, Jul 1944-Dec 1944 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Schwartz, Pinchos, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Schwartz, Pinchos: U.S. Tour, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Schwartz, Pinchos, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Sherman, Charles B., 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Sherman, Charles B., 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 13)
        Reel#: 13
      - Sherman, Charles B., 1943-1947 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Soloman, Charles, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Tabachinsky, Benjamin, Jan 1941-Apr 1941 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Tabachinsky, Benjamin, May 1941-Dec 1941 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Tabachinsky, Benjamin, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Tabachinsky, Benjamin, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Tabachinsky, Benjamin, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Tabachinsky, Benjamin, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Tabachinsky, Benjamin, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Tabachinsky, Benjamin: U.S. Campaign, Jan 1946-Mar 1946 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Tabachinsky, Benjamin: U.S. Campaign, Apr 1946-Jul 1946 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Tabachinsky, Benjamin, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 25)
        Reel#: 14
      - Vladeck, B. Charney, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Zimmerman, Charles, 1945-1946 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Sub Subseries 1C3: Correspondence: With Other Organizations (arranged alphabetically)
      - A. Berkman's Russian Aid Fund, 1942-1944 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - American Association for a Democratic Germany, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - American Association for a Democratic Germany, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - American Committee for the Jews in Poland, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - American Committee for the Protection of Foreign Born, 1939-1942 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - American Committee of OSE, 1943-1947 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - American Federation for Lithuanian Jews, 1942-1946 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - American Federation for Polish Jews, 1943, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - American Federation of Democratic Hungarians, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - American Federation of Democratic Hungarians, 1944-1946 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - American Federation of Labor (AFL), 1934-1939 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - AFL, 1940-1945 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - AFL, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - American Federation of Polish Jews, 1944, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 15)
        Reel#: 15
      - American Friends of Polish Jews, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - American Friends Service Committee, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - American Jewish Committee, 1941-1942, 1946, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - American Jewish Conference, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - American Jewish Congress, 1934-1941 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - American Jewish Congress, 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - American Jewish Congress, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - American Jewish Labor Council, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, 1935, 1937-1939 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, 1940-1943 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, 1944-1947 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - American Labor Archive and Research Institute, Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - American Labor Archive and Research Institute, Inc., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - American Labor Committee on International Affairs, 1942-1945 (Box 7, Folder 29)
      - American Labor Committee to Aid British Labor, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - American Labor Conference on International Affairs, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 31)
      - American Labor Conference on International Affairs, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 32)
      - American Memorial to Six Million Jews of Europe, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - American ORT Federation, 1938-1945 (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - American Red Cross, 1941-1943 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - American Red Cross, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - American Red Cross, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 37)
        Reel#: 16
      - American Red Cross, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 38)
      - American Red Cross, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 39)
      - American Red Magen David for Palestine, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - American Theatre Wing War Service, Inc., 1946 (Box 7, Folder 41)
      - American Relief for France, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 42)
      - American Zionist Emergency Council, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 43)
      - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, 1942-1947 (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - Association for Jewish Farm Settlements, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 45)
      - Austrian Labor Committee, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 46)
      - Bessarabian Federation of American Jews, 1944-1947 (Box 7, Folder 47)
      - Bialystocker Relief Committee of America, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 48)
      - B'nai B'rith, 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 49)
      - British War Relief, Inc., 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 50)
      - Brooklyn Jewish Community Council, 1943-1947 (Box 7, Folder 51)
      - Cooperative for American Remittances to Europe, 1945-1947 (Box 7, Folder 52)
      - Central Yiddish Cultural Organization (CYCO), 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 53)
      - CYCO, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 54)
      - CYCO, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 55)
      - Citizens Committee on Displaced Persons, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 56)
      - Civil Rights Defense Committee, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 57)
      - Committee for Cultural Freedom, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 58)
      - Committee for Polish Freedom, 1941-1942 (Box 7, Folder 59)
      - Committee for the Study of Recent Immigration from Europe, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 60)
      - Committee of Jewish Writers and Artists, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 61)
      - Committee on Special Refugee Problems, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 62)
      - Common Council for American Unity, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 63)
      - Common Council for American Unity, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 64)
      - Common Council for American Unity, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 1)
        Reel#: 17
      - Common Council for American Unity, 1946-1947 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Conference on Jewish Relations, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Conference on Jewish Relations, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO), 1943 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - CIO, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - CIO, 1946-1947 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - CIO: National War Relief Committee, 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Coordinating Committee of Jewish Organizations Dealing with Employment in War Industries, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Coordinating Committee of Jewish Organizations Dealing with Employment in War Industries, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Council for Democracy, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Council for the Underground Labor Movement..., 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Council for the Underground Labor Movement..., 1944-1946 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Council of Jewish Federations and Welfare Funds (CJFWF), 1934-1939 (Box 8, Folder 14)
        Reel#: 18
      - CJFWF, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - CJFWF, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - CJFWF, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - CJFWF, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - CJFWF, 1946-1947 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Demokratische Fluchtlingsfursorge, 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Descendants of the American Revolution, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Dominican Republic Settlement Association, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Federation of Jewish Charities, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - Federation of Jewish Charities, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - Federation of Jewish Charities, 1946-1947 (Box 8, Folder 25)
      - Federation of Lithuanian Jews, 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 26)
      - Federation of Polish Political Refugees in the USA, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - Fight for Freedom, Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - Forward Association, 1943-1946 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      - Forward Association, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 30)
        Reel#: 19
      - Freeland League, 1946-1947 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      - Friends of Austrian Labor, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - Fund for Jewish Refugee Writers, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 33)
      - General Jewish Council: Minutes, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 34)
      - General Jewish Council, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 35)
      - General Jewish Council: Minutes, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 36)
      - General Jewish Council, Jan 1939-Jul 1939 (Box 8, Folder 37)
      - General Jewish Council, Aug 1939-Dec 1939 (Box 8, Folder 38)
      - General Jewish Council: Minutes, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - General Jewish Council, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - General Jewish Council, 1942-1943 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - German-Jewish Children's Aid, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 4)
        Reel#: 20
      - German-Jewish Children's Aid, 1937-1939 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - German Labor Delegation in the U.S., 1939-1946 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Hashomer Hatzair, 1944-1945 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS), 1939-1940 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - HIAS, 1940-1942 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - HIAS, 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - HIAS, 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Histadrut: Delegation to America, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Institute of Social Research, Columbia University, 1944-1947 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - International Federation of Trade Unions, 1935-1939 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - International Labor Organization, 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - International Relief Association, 1939-1942 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - International Rescue & Relief Committee, 1942-1947 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - International Solidarity Committee, 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - International Workers Order, 1935, 1942, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Italian-American Labor Council, 1945-1947 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Italian-American Labor Council, 1940-1943 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Jewish Children's Overseas Fund, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - Jewish Labor Bund, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - Jewish Labor Bund, 1940-1945 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - Jewish Labor Bund, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      - Jewish Labor Bund, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      - Jewish Latvian Relief, Inc., 1947 (Box 9, Folder 27)
        Reel#: 21
      - Jewish National Workers Alliance, 1937-1946 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      - Jewish Occupational Council, 1938-1940 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      - Jewish Occupational Council, 1941-1947 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      - Jewish Peoples Committee, 1937-1940 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      - Jewish Social Research Foundation, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      - Jewish Socialist Verband, 1935-1940 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      - Jewish Socialist Verband, 1940-1944 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      - Jewish Socialist Verband, 1945-1947 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      - Jewish Statistical Bureau, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 36)
      - Jewish Statistical Bureau, 1941-1944 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      - Jews from France, Inc, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 38)
      - Joint Boycott Council, 1935-1936 (Box 9, Folder 39)
      - Joint Boycott Council, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      - Joint Boycott Council, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 41)
      - Joint Boycott Council, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 42)
        Reel#: 22
      - Joint Boycott Council, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 43)
      - Joint Relief Committee: Havana, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Labor Education Service, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Labor League for Human Rights, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Labor League for Human Rights, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Labor League for Human Rights, 1944-1947 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Landsmanshaftn, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - League against Fascism and Dictatorship, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - League for Human Rights, Freedom and Democracy, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - League for Human Rights, Freedom and Democracy, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - League for Industrial Democracy, 1942-1946 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - National Coat & Suit Industry Recovery Board, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Left Poale Zion, 1937-1942 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Left Poale Zion, 1943-1945 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Left Poale Zion, 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - National Committee for Labor Palestine, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - National Committee on Post-war Immigration Policy, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - National Committee to Combat Anti-Semitism, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC), 1943-1944 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - NCRAC, 1945-1946 (Box 10, Folder 19)
        Reel#: 23
      - NCRAC, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1941-1945 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      - National Conference of Jewish Social Welfare, 1943-1944 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - National Council of Jewish Women, 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      - National Fair Rent Committee, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - National Jewish Welfare Board, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      - National Jewish Welfare Board, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - National Jewish Welfare Board, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      - National Jewish Welfare Board, 1943-1944 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      - National Jewish Welfare Board, 1945-1947 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      - National Negro Congress, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      - National Organization of Polish Jews, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 31)
      - National Refugee Service, 1937-1939 (Box 10, Folder 32)
      - National Refugee Service, 1918-Mar 1941 (Box 10, Folder 33)
        Reel#: 24
      - National Refugee Service, May 1941-1943 (Box 10, Folder 34)
      - National Refugee Service, 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 35)
      - National Refugee Service, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 36)
      - Negro Labor Committee, 1941-1943 (Box 10, Folder 37)
      - New School for Social Research, 1940-1943 (Box 10, Folder 38)
      - New School for Social Research, 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 39)
      - Poale Zion, 1934-1944 (Box 10, Folder 40)
      - Post-war World Council, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - Polish Women's Relief Committee, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - President's Advisory Committee on Political Refugees, 1942-1943 (Box 10, Folder 43)
      - Public National Bank & Trust Co., 1945 (Box 10, Folder 44)
      - Public National Bank & Trust Co., 1946 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      - Public National Bank & Trust Co., 1947 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - Rand School of Social Science, 1938-1947 (Box 10, Folder 47)
      - Roumanian Labor League, Jan 1937-Apr 1937 (Box 11, Folder 1)
        Reel#: 25
      - Roumanian Labor League, May 1937-Dec 1937 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Roumanian Labor League, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Roumanian Labor League, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Roumanian Labor League, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Roumanian Labor League, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Roumanian Labor League, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Roumanian Labor League, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Roumanian Labor League, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Roumanian Labor League, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Roumanian Labor League, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Roumanian Labor League (subscription list), 1946-1947 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Roumanian Labor League, Jan 1947-Mar 1947 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Roumanian Labor League, Apr 1947-Jun 1947 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Roumanian Labor League, Jul 1947-Dec 1947 (Box 11, Folder 15)
        Reel#: 26
      - Roumanian Labor League, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Russian Social Democrats, 1941-1944 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Russian Socialist Revolutionary, 1941-1942 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Party: New York Group (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_d848393a083c72a6654c820b42a86814)
      - Social Democratic Federation, 1938-1947 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Socialist Party of the U.S., 1934-1935 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Socialist Party of the U.S., 1937-1940 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Synagogue Council of America, 1942-1943 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - Union for Democratic Action, 1941-1946 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - Union for the Protection of the Human Person, 1940-1947 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - Union of American Hebrew Congregations, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 24A)
      - Union of Jews from France, 1945-1946 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - Union of Russian Jews, 1943-1945 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - Union of Russian Jews, 1946-1947 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - Unions: General, 1934-1939 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - Unions: General, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - Unions: General, 1942-1943 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      - Unions: General, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 31)
      - Unions: General, 1946-1947 (Box 11, Folder 32)
      - Unions: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (ACWA), 1934-1936 (Box 11, Folder 33)
      - Unions: ACWA, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 34)
      - Unions: ACWA, 1943-1947 (Box 11, Folder 35)
        Reel#: 27
      - Unions: ACWA: Joint Boards, 1934-1937 (Box 11, Folder 36)
      - Unions: ACWA: Joint Boards, 1942-1947 (Box 11, Folder 37)
      - Unions: ACWA: Locals, 1934-1944 (Box 11, Folder 38)
      - Unions: ACWA: Locals, 1945-1947 (Box 11, Folder 39)
      - Unions: American Federation of Office Employees, 1943-1946 (Box 11, Folder 40)
      - Unions: Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paper Hangers, 1934-1947 (Box 11, Folder 41)
      - Unions: Hebrew-American Typographical Union, 1934, 1940-1947 (Box 11, Folder 42)
      - Unions: Hebrew Actors Union, 1939-1947, undated (Box 11, Folder 43)
      - Unions: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1940-1947 (Box 11, Folder 44)
      - Unions: International Fur Workers Union, 1935-1941 (Box 11, Folder 45)
      - Unions: International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU), 1935-1939 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Unions: ILGWU, 1940-1942 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Unions: ILGWU, 1943-1944 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Unions: ILGWU, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Unions: ILGWU, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Unions: ILGWU, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Unions: ILGWU: Joint Board Cloak...Makers, 1934-1939 (Box 12, Folder 7)